sti.edu 2005-12-14

# STI Colleges and Education Centers

Privacy Policy 

Introduction 

This is the website of STI College. We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

Website Administration 

| School name:  | STI Colleges and Education Centers  
---|---  
Address :  | 7/F Phil. First Building, 6764 Ayala Avenue   
Makati City 1229, Philippines   
Website URL:  | [_http://www.sti.edu_](http://www.sti.edu/)  
Website e-mail: | [_inquire@stihq.net_](mailto:inquire@stihq.net)  

Information Collection and Use

We respect each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

**For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.**

The information we collect is:

  * used to improved the content of our Web page
  * used to notify visitors about updates to our Web site.
  * never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

With respect to cookies. We do not set any cookies. 

Registration is not required to enter our website.

We have submission forms.

We require information from user on our submission forms. A user must provide contact information (such as name, e-mail, and current location). Upon the approval of submission, we use the information to contact the user.

We never sell or share our users' e-mail addresses. 

Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. 

Conflict Resolution

We are committed to resolving disputes within 24-48 hours. If the problem arises, users may _contact_ us by [_email_](mailto:inquire@stihq.net) or telephone. 

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy please contact us at: 

**STI Colleges and Education Centers**  
7/F Phil. First Building  
6764 Ayala Avenue, Makati City   
1229 Philippines   
Tel. (632) 887-8447  
Fax. (632) 891-3725
